



 

   //Questions array

   let questions = [

    {

         number:1,

         question: "__ is a group of sentences or single sometimes that forms a meaningful unit",

         answer : "Paragraph",

         options : [

                          "Clause",

                          "Paragraph",

                          "Phrase",

                          "Sentence"

                        ]

    

    },

    {

         number:2,

         question: "Which of these is not a component of paragraph",

         answer : "Introductory sentence",

         options : [

                          "Introductory sentence",

                          "Topic sentence",

                          "Supporting details",

                          "Concluding sentence"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:3,

         question: "___ introduces the main idea",

         answer : "Topic sentence",

         options : [

                          "Introductory sentence",

                          "Topic sentence",

                          "Supporting details",

                          "Concluding sentence"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:4,

         question: "The steps to writing a good paragraph include these except",

         answer : "The organising stage",

         options : [

                          "The prewriting stage",

                          "The publishing stage",

                          "The organising stage",

                          "The writing stage"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:5,

         question: "At which stage of paragraph writing does the writer carefully organise his ideas",

         answer : "The prewriting stage",

         options : [

                          "The prewriting stage",

                          "The publishing stage",

                          "The organising stage",

                          "The writing stage"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:6,

         question: "The stage of thinking what to write is",

         answer : "Brainstorming",

         options : [

                          "Drafting",

                          "Brainstorming",

                          "Research",

                          "Organising"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:7,

         question: "__ involves writing down your own ideas quickly without worrying about being perfect or staying on topic",

         answer : "Drafting",

         options : [

                          "Drafting",

                          "Prosetry",

                          "Research",

                          "Crafting"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:8,

         question: "Effective paragraphs have five main characteristics. Which of these not among them",

         answer : "Punctuation",

         options : [

                          "Unity",

                          "Adequate development",

                          "Punctuation",

                          "Topic sentence"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:9,

         question: "___ refers to the extent to which all ideas contained within a given paragraph harmoniously relate",

         answer : "Unity",

         options : [

                          "Unity",

                          "Adequate development",

                          "Punctuation",

                          "Topic sentence"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:10,

         question: "In paragraph writing, coherence rests on__",

         answer : "Logical progression",

         options : [

                          "Unity",

                          "Adequate development",

                          "Logical progression",

                          "Variety"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:11,

         question: "An effective device for ensuring unity in a paragraph is",

         answer : "Topic sentence",

         options : [

                          "Variety",

                          "Adequate development",

                          "Coherence",

                          "Topic sentence"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:12,

         question: "Words that specify relationship between sentences and between paragraphs are called",

         answer : "Transitional words",

         options : [

                          "Linking verbs",

                          "Verbal bridges",

                          "Subordinators",

                          "Transitional words"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:13,

         question: "Adding sentence variety to ___ can give it to life and rhythm",

         answer : "Prose",

         options : [

                          "Sentence",

                          "Prose",

                          "Poetry",

                          "Paragraph"  

                          ]

    

    }

     ];   